(Sheldon:)A hush falls over the crowd
as Cooper studies the board.
(Sheldon:)He makes his move.
(Sheldon:)He's dividing both sides by I,
he's adding back the coefficient.
(Sheldon:)He has a value for P.
He's plugging that back in.
(Sheldon:)He takes the derivative
and he solves the equation.
- Crowd goes wild. "Nobel, Nobel!"
- Cooper.
"Nobel." Kripke.
Yeah... Don't look at my board.
- What's that?
- That's a drawing of a really cool train.
Yeah, don't look at that, either.
(Sheldon:)- What do you want?
- I have some bad news.
You're working on a grant proposal
for a new fusion reactor.
I'm working on a grant proposal
The university is only allowed
to submit one proposal.
(Sheldon:)So they asked you to pack up your things
and ship out. That's hard cheese, Barry.
(Sheldon:)You're one of the good ones.
(Kripke:)No, they're making us work together.